<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Posts on kakono</title>
    <link>/post/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Posts on kakono</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 11 Mar 2020 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="/post/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Post processing ADCP data</title>
      <link>/post/post-processing-adcp-data/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 11 Mar 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/post/post-processing-adcp-data/</guid>
      <description>To-date no standardized technique exists for combining velocity data from multiple ADCP transects to produce a composite depiction of three-dimensional velocity fields (Figure 1. To address this important need, the a new software tool has been developed, the Velocity Mapping Toolbox (VMT), for processing, analyzing, and displaying velocity data collected along multiple ADCP transects. VMT can be run using either the Matlab® source code or compiled standalone executables.
Users with access to Matlab® are encouraged to run the source code for the most versatility.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The bathmetry measurement begins with base stations</title>
      <link>/post/the-bathmetry-measurement-begins-with-base-stations/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 11 Mar 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/post/the-bathmetry-measurement-begins-with-base-stations/</guid>
      <description>ASSEMBLYOnce arriving on site, set up is relatively quick. The best place to park and the best point to launch the boat is scoped on foot. This is usually provided by maintenance access ways which are pathways built into pond designs to allow for machinery to access the pond for dredging. The boat is assembled near the launch point into the pond. This requires attaching the propellers to the rear of the boat, connecting and strapping in the boat batteries, positioning the ADCP into the holder in the centre of the boat, and connecting the cables to the Program Control Module (PCM), radio and GPS.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>